[
{ "question": "CAPITAL CITIES ğŸŒ\n\n What is the capital city of Belgium?", "answer": "Brussels" },
{ "question": "CAPITAL CITIES ğŸŒ\n\n What is the capital city of Belarus?", "answer": "Minsk" },
{ "question": "CAPITAL CITIES ğŸŒ\n\n What is the capital city of Honduras?", "answer": "Tegucigalpa" },
{ "question": "CAPITAL CITIES ğŸŒ\n\n What is the capital city of Iran?", "answer": "Tehran" },
{ "question": "CAPITAL CITIES ğŸŒ\n\n What is the capital city of Greece?", "answer": "Athens" },
{ "question": "CAPITAL CITIES ğŸŒ\n\n What is the capital city of Bangladesh?", "answer": "Dhaka" },
{ "question": "CAPITAL CITIES ğŸŒ\n\n What is the capital city of Bolivia?", "answer": "La Paz" },
{ "question": "CAPITAL CITIES ğŸŒ\n\n What is the capital city of Finland?", "answer": "Helsinki" },
{ "question": "CAPITAL CITIES ğŸŒ\n\n What is the capital city of Bosnia and Herzegovina?", "answer": "Sarajevo" },
{ "question": "CAPITAL CITIES ğŸŒ\n\n What is the capital city of Fiji?", "answer": "Suva" },
{ "question": "CAPITAL CITIES ğŸŒ\n\n What is the capital city of Armenia?", "answer": "Yerevan" },
{ "question": "CAPITAL CITIES ğŸŒ\n\n What is the capital city of Cyprus?", "answer": "Nicosia" },
{ "question": "CAPITAL CITIES ğŸŒ\n\n What is the capital city of Botswana?", "answer": "Gaborone" },
{ "question": "CAPITAL CITIES ğŸŒ\n\n What is the capital city of Iraq?", "answer": "Baghdad" },
{ "question": "CAPITAL CITIES ğŸŒ\n\n What is the capital city of Iceland?", "answer": "ReykjavÃ­k" },
{ "question": "CAPITAL CITIES ğŸŒ\n\n What is the capital city of Belgium?", "answer": "Brussels" },
{ "question": "CAPITAL CITIES ğŸŒ\n\n What is the capital city of Bulgaria?", "answer": "Sofia" },
{ "question": "CAPITAL CITIES ğŸŒ\n\n What is the capital city of Australia?", "answer": "Canberra" },
{ "question": "CAPITAL CITIES ğŸŒ\n\n What is the capital city of Cuba?", "answer": "Havana" },
{ "question": "CAPITAL CITIES ğŸŒ\n\n What is the capital city of Estonia?", "answer": "Tallinn" },
{ "question": "CAPITAL CITIES ğŸŒ\n\n What is the capital city of Ecuador?", "answer": "Quito" },
{ "question": "CAPITAL CITIES ğŸŒ\n\n What is the capital city of Canada?", "answer": "Ottawa" },
{ "question": "CAPITAL CITIES ğŸŒ\n\n What is the capital city of Georgia?", "answer": "Tbilisi" },
{ "question": "CAPITAL CITIES ğŸŒ\n\n What is the capital city of Angola?", "answer": "Luanda" },
{ "question": "CAPITAL CITIES ğŸŒ\n\n What is the capital city of Albania?", "answer": "Tirana" },
{ "question": "CAPITAL CITIES ğŸŒ\n\n What is the capital city of Denmark?", "answer": "Copenhagen" },
{ "question": "CAPITAL CITIES ğŸŒ\n\n What is the capital city of Egypt?", "answer": "Cairo" },
{ "question": "CAPITAL CITIES ğŸŒ\n\n What is the capital city of Ghana?", "answer": "Accra" },
{ "question": "CAPITAL CITIES ğŸŒ\n\n What is the capital city of Italy?", "answer": "Rome" },
{ "question": "CAPITAL CITIES ğŸŒ\n\n What is the capital city of Nigeria?", "answer": "Abuja" },
{ "question": "CAPITAL CITIES ğŸŒ\n\n What is the capital city of Ireland?", "answer": "Dublin" },
{ "question": "CAPITAL CITIES ğŸŒ\n\n What is the capital city of Sudan?", "answer": "Khartoum" },
{ "question": "CAPITAL CITIES ğŸŒ\n\n What is the capital city of Czech Republic?", "answer": "Prague" },
{ "question": "CAPITAL CITIES ğŸŒ\n\n What is the capital city of Cameroon?", "answer": "Yaounde" },
{ "question": "CAPITAL CITIES ğŸŒ\n\n What is the capital city of Chile?", "answer": "Santiago" },
{ "question": "CAPITAL CITIES ğŸŒ\n\n What is the capital city of Azerbaijan?", "answer": "Baku" },
{ "question": "CAPITAL CITIES ğŸŒ\n\n What is the capital city of Indonesia?", "answer": "Jakarta" },
{ "question": "CAPITAL CITIES ğŸŒ\n\n What is the capital city of Afghanistan?", "answer": "Kabul" },
{ "question": "CAPITAL CITIES ğŸŒ\n\n Which country has the capital Zagreb?", "answer": "Croatia" },
{ "question": "CAPITAL CITIES ğŸŒ\n\n Which country has the capital city of Belmopan?", "answer": "Belize" },
{ "question": "CAPITAL CITIES ğŸŒ\n\n Which country has the capital city of Riga?", "answer": "Latvia" },
{ "question": "CAPITAL CITIES ğŸŒ\n\n Which country has the capital city of Luanda?", "answer": "Angola" },
{ "question": "CAPITAL CITIES ğŸŒ\n\n Which country has the capital city of Rabat?", "answer": "Morocco" },
{ "question": "CAPITAL CITIES ğŸŒ\n\n Which country has the capital city of Montevideo?", "answer": "Uruguay" },
{ "question": "CAPITAL CITIES ğŸŒ\n\n Which country has the capital city of Muscat?", "answer": "Oman" },
    
{ "question": "U.S. STATE CAPITALS ğŸŒ\n\n What is the state capital of West Virginia?", "answer": "Charleston" },
{ "question": "U.S. STATE CAPITALS ğŸŒ\n\n What is the state capital of New Jersey?", "answer": "Trenton" },
{ "question": "U.S. STATE CAPITALS ğŸŒ\n\n What is the state capital of South Dakota?", "answer": "Pierre" },
{ "question": "U.S. STATE CAPITALS ğŸŒ\n\n What is the state capital of Arizona?", "answer": "Phoenix" },
{ "question": "U.S. STATE CAPITALS ğŸŒ\n\n What is the state capital of Illinois?", "answer": "Springfield" },
{ "question": "U.S. STATE CAPITALS ğŸŒ\n\n What is the state capital of Nebraska?", "answer": "Lincoln" },
{ "question": "U.S. STATE CAPITALS ğŸŒ\n\n What is the state capital of Texas?", "answer": "Austin" },
{ "question": "U.S. STATE CAPITALS ğŸŒ\n\n What is the state capital of California?", "answer": "Sacramento" },
{ "question": "U.S. STATE CAPITALS ğŸŒ\n\n What is the state capital of Alaska?", "answer": "Juneau" },
{ "question": "U.S. STATE CAPITALS ğŸŒ\n\n What is the state capital of Colorado?", "answer": "Denver" },
{ "question": "U.S. STATE CAPITALS ğŸŒ\n\n What is the state capital of Georgia?", "answer": "Atlanta" },
{ "question": "U.S. STATE CAPITALS ğŸŒ\n\n What is the state capital of Oregon?", "answer": "Salem" },
{ "question": "U.S. STATE CAPITALS ğŸŒ\n\n What is the state capital of Louisiana?", "answer": "Baton Rouge" },
{ "question": "U.S. STATE CAPITALS ğŸŒ\n\n What is the state capital of Vermont?", "answer": "Montpelier" },
{ "question": "U.S. STATE CAPITALS ğŸŒ\n\n What is the state capital of New York?", "answer": "Albany" },
{ "question": "U.S. STATE CAPITALS ğŸŒ\n\n What is the state capital of Utah?", "answer": "Salt Lake City" },
{ "question": "U.S. STATE CAPITALS ğŸŒ\n\n What is the state capital of Washington?", "answer": "Olympia" },
{ "question": "U.S. STATE CAPITALS ğŸŒ\n\n What is the state capital of Iowa?", "answer": "Des Moines" },
{ "question": "U.S. STATE CAPITALS ğŸŒ\n\n What is the state capital of Hawaii?", "answer": "Honolulu" },
    
{ "question": "WORLD RIVERS ğŸŒ\n\n What is the longest river in the world?", "answer": "Nile" },
{ "question": "WORLD RIVERS ğŸŒ\n\n Which river flows through the city of Paris?", "answer": "Seine" },
{ "question": "WORLD RIVERS ğŸŒ\n\n Which river runs through Baghdad?", "answer": "Tigris" },
{ "question": "WORLD RIVERS ğŸŒ\n\n Which river forms part of the border between Mexico and the United States?", "answer": "Rio Grande" },
{ "question": "WORLD RIVERS ğŸŒ\n\n Which river flows through Budapest, Vienna and Bratislava?", "answer": "Danube" },
{ "question": "WORLD RIVERS ğŸŒ\n\n Which river runs through London?", "answer": "Thames" },
{ "question": "WORLD RIVERS ğŸŒ\n\n Which river flows through Rome?", "answer": "Tiber" },
{ "question": "WORLD RIVERS ğŸŒ\n\n Which river is sacred in Hinduism and flows through Varanasi?", "answer": "Ganges" },
{ "question": "WORLD RIVERS ğŸŒ\n\n Which African river is known for Victoria Falls?", "answer": "Zambezi" },
{ "question": "WORLD RIVERS ğŸŒ\n\n Which river flows through the Grand Canyon?", "answer": "Colorado" },
{ "question": "WORLD RIVERS ğŸŒ\n\n Which river is the longest in China?", "answer": "Yangtze" },
{ "question": "WORLD RIVERS ğŸŒ\n\n Which river separates the cities of Minneapolis and St. Paul?", "answer": "Mississippi" },
{ "question": "WORLD RIVERS ğŸŒ\n\n Which river flows through the German city of Cologne?", "answer": "Rhine" },
{ "question": "WORLD RIVERS ğŸŒ\n\n Which river flows through the city of Dublin?", "answer": "Liffey" },
{ "question": "WORLD RIVERS ğŸŒ\n\n Which river is the longest in England?", "answer": "Severn" },

  { "question": "AMERICAN FOOTBALL ğŸˆ\n\n Which NFL team has the nickname Seahawks?", "answer": "Seattle" },
  { "question": "AMERICAN FOOTBALL ğŸˆ\n\n Which NFL team has the nickname Ravens?", "answer": "Baltimore" },
  { "question": "AMERICAN FOOTBALL ğŸˆ\n\n Which NFL team has the nickname Jaguars?", "answer": "Jacksonville" },
  { "question": "AMERICAN FOOTBALL ğŸˆ\n\n What is the nickname of the Denver NFL team?", "answer": "Broncos" },
  { "question": "AMERICAN FOOTBALL ğŸˆ\n\n What is the nickname of the Green Bay NFL team?", "answer": "Packers" },
  { "question": "AMERICAN FOOTBALL ğŸˆ\n\n What is the nickname of the Pittsburgh NFL team?", "answer": "Steelers" },
  { "question": "AMERICAN FOOTBALL ğŸˆ\n\n What is the nickname of the Cincinnati NFL team?", "answer": "Bengals" },
  { "question": "AMERICAN FOOTBALL ğŸˆ\n\n What is the nickname of the Cleveland NFL team?", "answer": "Browns" },
  { "question": "AMERICAN FOOTBALL ğŸˆ\n\n What is the nickname of the Baltimore NFL team?", "answer": "Ravens" },
  { "question": "AMERICAN FOOTBALL ğŸˆ\n\n What is the nickname of the Kansas City NFL team?", "answer": "Chiefs" },
  { "question": "AMERICAN FOOTBALL ğŸˆ\n\n What is the nickname of the New Orleans NFL team?", "answer": "Saints" },
  { "question": "AMERICAN FOOTBALL ğŸˆ\n\n What is the nickname of the Tampa Bay NFL team?", "answer": "Buccaneers" },
  { "question": "AMERICAN FOOTBALL ğŸˆ\n\n What is the nickname of the Las Vegas NFL team?", "answer": "Raiders" },

  { "question": "ART ğŸ¨\n\n Who painted 'The Night Watch'?", "answer": "Rembrandt" },
  { "question": "ART ğŸ¨\n\n Which artist painted the 'School of Athens'?", "answer": "Raphael" },
  { "question": "ART ğŸ¨\n\n Which artist is known for creating 'Guernica'?", "answer": "Picasso" },

{ "question": "BASEBALL âš¾\n\n What is the nickname of the St. Louis baseball team?", "answer": "Cardinals" },
{ "question": "BASEBALL âš¾\n\n What is the nickname of the Toronto baseball team?", "answer": "Blue Jays" },
{ "question": "BASEBALL âš¾\n\n What is the nickname of the Houston baseball team?", "answer": "Astros" },
{ "question": "BASEBALL âš¾\n\n What is the nickname of the Detroit baseball team?", "answer": "Tigers" },
{ "question": "BASEBALL âš¾\n\n What is the nickname of the Milwaukee baseball team?", "answer": "Brewers" },
{ "question": "BASEBALL âš¾\n\n What is the nickname of the Chicago baseball team in the National League?", "answer": "Cubs" },
{ "question": "BASEBALL âš¾\n\n What is the nickname of the Boston baseball team?", "answer": "Red Sox" },
{ "question": "BASEBALL âš¾\n\n What is the nickname of the Los Angeles baseball team in the National League?", "answer": "Dodgers" },
{ "question": "BASEBALL âš¾\n\n What is the nickname of the San Francisco baseball team?", "answer": "Giants" },

  { "question": "BASKETBALL ğŸ€\n\n What is the nickname of the Chicago Bulls' NBA team mascot?", "answer": "Benny" },
  { "question": "BASKETBALL ğŸ€\n\n What is the nickname of the Dallas NBA team?", "answer": "Mavericks" },
  { "question": "BASKETBALL ğŸ€\n\n What is the nickname of the Detroit basketball team?", "answer": "Pistons" },
  { "question": "BASKETBALL ğŸ€\n\n What is the nickname of the Boston basketball team?", "answer": "Celtics" },
  { "question": "BASKETBALL ğŸ€\n\n What is the nickname of the Miami NBA team?", "answer": "Heat" },
  { "question": "BASKETBALL ğŸ€\n\n What is the nickname of the Orlando NBA team?", "answer": "Magic" },
  { "question": "BASKETBALL ğŸ€\n\n What is the nickname of the Houston NBA team?", "answer": "Rockets" },
  { "question": "BASKETBALL ğŸ€\n\n What is the nickname of the San Antonio NBA team?", "answer": "Spurs" },
  { "question": "BASKETBALL ğŸ€\n\n What is the nickname of the Milwaukee NBA team?", "answer": "Bucks" },

  { "question": "CHEMISTRY ğŸ§ª\n\n What element has the atomic number 6?", "answer": "Carbon" },
  { "question": "CHEMISTRY ğŸ§ª\n\n What element is diamond made of?", "answer": "Carbon" },
  { "question": "CHEMISTRY ğŸ§ª\n\n What is the chemical symbol for Sodium?", "answer": "Na" },
  { "question": "CHEMISTRY ğŸ§ª\n\n What is the symbol for the element Potassium?", "answer": "K" },
  { "question": "CHEMISTRY ğŸ§ª\n\n What is the symbol for the element Mercury?", "answer": "Hg" },
  { "question": "CHEMISTRY ğŸ§ª\n\n What is the pH of pure water?", "answer": "7" },
  { "question": "CHEMISTRY ğŸ§ª\n\n What is the only metal that is liquid at room temperature?", "answer": "Mercury" },

{ "question": "COMICS ğŸ¦¸\n\n Which metal is bonded to Wolverine's skeleton?", "answer": "Adamantium" },
{ "question": "COMICS ğŸ¦¸\n\n Who created the Marvel characters Spider-Man and the X-Men?", "answer": "Stan Lee" },
{ "question": "COMICS ğŸ¦¸\n\n Which DC superhero can run at superhuman speed?", "answer": "Flash" },
{ "question": "COMICS ğŸ¦¸\n\n What is the name of Superman's home planet?", "answer": "Krypton" },
{ "question": "COMICS ğŸ¦¸\n\n Which Batman villain is also known as Oswald Cobblepot?", "answer": "Penguin" },
{ "question": "COMICS ğŸ¦¸\n\n Which comic book series introduced the character Rorschach?", "answer": "Watchmen" },

  { "question": "MOVIES ğŸ¬\n\n In 'The Godfather', which five-letter word is suprisingly absent from the film's script?", "answer": "Mafia" },
  { "question": "MOVIES ğŸ¬\n\n Who directed 'Jurassic Park'?", "answer": "Spielberg" },
  { "question": "MOVIES ğŸ¬\n\n Who directed the 2019 film 'Once Upon a Time in Hollywood'?", "answer": "Tarantino" },
  { "question": "MOVIES ğŸ¬\n\n In which movie is the fictional planet Pandora?", "answer": "Avatar" },
  { "question": "MOVIES ğŸ¬\n\n In what movie does the phrase 'Here's looking at you, kid' appear?", "answer": "Casablanca" },
  { "question": "MOVIES ğŸ¬\n\n What 2019 foreign-language film won the Academy Award for Best Picture?", "answer": "Parasite" },
  { "question": "MOVIES ğŸ¬\n\n Complete the name of this Dumb and Dumber character played by Jim Carrey: Lloyd _______?", "answer": "Christmas" },
  { "question": "MOVIES ğŸ¬\n\n In the Star Wars film series, which desert planet is home to Luke Skywalker?", "answer": "Tatooine" },
  { "question": "MOVIES ğŸ¬\n\n In what 1986 fantasy film does David Bowie star as Jareth, the King of the Goblins?", "answer": "Labyrinth" },

{ "question": "CURRENCY ğŸ’°\n\n What is the currency of Japan?", "answer": "Yen" },
{ "question": "CURRENCY ğŸ’°\n\n What is the currency of Singapore?", "answer": "Dollar" },
{ "question": "CURRENCY ğŸ’°\n\n What is the currency of Somalia?", "answer": "Shilling" },
{ "question": "CURRENCY ğŸ’°\n\n What is the currency of South Africa?", "answer": "Rand" },
{ "question": "CURRENCY ğŸ’°\n\n What is the currency of Switzerland?", "answer": "Franc" },
{ "question": "CURRENCY ğŸ’°\n\n What is the currency of South Korea?", "answer": "Won" },
{ "question": "CURRENCY ğŸ’°\n\n What is the currency of Brazil?", "answer": "Real" },
{ "question": "CURRENCY ğŸ’°\n\n What is the currency of Russia?", "answer": "Ruble" },
{ "question": "CURRENCY ğŸ’°\n\n What is the currency of India?", "answer": "Rupee" },
{ "question": "CURRENCY ğŸ’°\n\n What is the currency of Mexico?", "answer": "Peso" },
{ "question": "CURRENCY ğŸ’°\n\n What is the currency of Egypt?", "answer": "Pound" },
{ "question": "CURRENCY ğŸ’°\n\n What is the currency of Turkey?", "answer": "Lira" },
{ "question": "CURRENCY ğŸ’°\n\n What is the currency of Argentina?", "answer": "Peso" },
{ "question": "CURRENCY ğŸ’°\n\n What is the currency of Norway?", "answer": "Krone" },
{ "question": "CURRENCY ğŸ’°\n\n What is the currency of Thailand?", "answer": "Baht" },

{ "question": "ENTERTAINMENT ğŸ¬\n\n What is the name of the fictional country in 'Black Panther'?", "answer": "Wakanda" },

{ "question": "FLAGS ğŸš©\n\n Which African country's flag features a single five-pointed green star on a red background?", "answer": "Morocco" },
{ "question": "FLAGS ğŸš©\n\n Which Scandinavian country has a blue flag with a yellow cross?", "answer": "Sweden" },
{ "question": "FLAGS ğŸš©\n\n Which Middle Eastern countryâ€™s flag features a cedar tree?", "answer": "Lebanon" },
{ "question": "FLAGS ğŸš©\n\n Which Caribbean nationâ€™s flag features a black trident?", "answer": "Barbados" },
{ "question": "FLAGS ğŸš©\n\n Which Asian countryâ€™s flag has a red background with five yellow stars?", "answer": "China" },
{ "question": "FLAGS ğŸš©\n\n What is the only flag that does not have four sides?", "answer": "Nepal" },
{ "question": "FLAGS ğŸš©\n\n The flag of which U.S. state contains a representation of the British 'Union Jack'?", "answer": "Hawaii" },
    
{ "question": "FOOD ğŸ•\n\n Manchego cheese originates from which country?", "answer": "Spain" },
{ "question": "FOOD ğŸ•\n\n In Japanese cuisine, what name is given to a salty paste made from fermented soybeans?", "answer": "Miso" },
{ "question": "FOOD ğŸ•\n\n Which fruit is dried to make prunes?", "answer": "Plums" },
{ "question": "FOOD ğŸ•\n\n The Italian name of which pasta shape translates to 'little worms'?", "answer": "Vermicelli" },
{ "question": "FOOD ğŸ•\n\n Which spice is harvested from the crocus plant?", "answer": "Saffron" },
{ "question": "FOOD ğŸ•\n\n In which country did the dish 'ceviche' originate?", "answer": "Peru" },
{ "question": "FOOD ğŸ•\n\n Which bean is used to make traditional baked beans?", "answer": "Haricot" },
{ "question": "FOOD ğŸ•\n\n Which fruit has varieties called Cavendish, Lady Finger, and Red?", "answer": "Banana" },
{ "question": "FOOD ğŸ•\n\n Edam cheese originates from which country?", "answer": "Netherlands" },
{ "question": "FOOD ğŸ•\n\n What is the main ingredient in hummus?", "answer": "Chickpea" },
{ "question": "FOOD ğŸ•\n\n Which Japanese dish consists of raw fish sliced thinly without rice?", "answer": "Sashimi" },
{ "question": "FOOD ğŸ•\n\n What type of nut is used to make marzipan?", "answer": "Almond" },
{ "question": "FOOD ğŸ•\n\n Which fruit is the base ingredient of guacamole?", "answer": "Avocado" },
{ "question": "FOOD ğŸ•\n\n Which fruit is used to produce the drink calvados?", "answer": "Apple" },
{ "question": "FOOD ğŸ•\n\n What type of pastry is traditionally used for Ã©clairs?", "answer": "Choux" },
{ "question": "FOOD ğŸ•\n\n What is the Japanese word for seaweed sheets used in sushi?", "answer": "Nori" },
{ "question": "FOOD ğŸ•\n\n Halloumi cheese is traditionally associated with which island?", "answer": "Cyprus" },
{ "question": "FOOD ğŸ•\n\n What is the Italian culinary term for finely chopped herbs mixed with garlic and lemon zest?", "answer": "Gremolata" },
{ "question": "FOOD ğŸ•\n\n Which nut is the key ingredient in Nutella?", "answer": "Hazelnut" },
{ "question": "FOOD ğŸ•\n\n Which Italian dessert literally translates to 'pick me up'?", "answer": "Tiramisu" },

  { "question": "GEOGRAPHY ğŸŒ\n\n What is the largest island in the world?", "answer": "Greenland" },
  { "question": "GEOGRAPHY ğŸŒ\n\n What is the only landlocked country in South America?", "answer": "Paraguay" },
  { "question": "GEOGRAPHY ğŸŒ\n\n Which country has the most time zones?", "answer": "France" },
  { "question": "GEOGRAPHY ğŸŒ\n\n Which country has a city named 'Dizzy', a reference to jazz legend Dizzy Gillespie?", "answer": "Cuba" },
  { "question": "GEOGRAPHY ğŸŒ\n\n Which country has the most volcanoes?", "answer": "Indonesia" },
  { "question": "GEOGRAPHY ğŸŒ\n\n What is the longest mountain range in the world?", "answer": "Andes" },
  { "question": "GEOGRAPHY ğŸŒ\n\n What country has the most islands?", "answer": "Sweden" },

{ "question": "ICE HOCKEY ğŸ’\n\n What is the nickname of the Carolina NHL team?", "answer": "Hurricanes" },
{ "question": "ICE HOCKEY ğŸ’\n\n What is the nickname of the Calgary NHL team?", "answer": "Flames" },
{ "question": "ICE HOCKEY ğŸ’\n\n What is the nickname of the Colorado NHL team?", "answer": "Avalanche" },
{ "question": "ICE HOCKEY ğŸ’\n\n What is the nickname of the Boston NHL team?", "answer": "Bruins" },
{ "question": "ICE HOCKEY ğŸ’\n\n What is the nickname of the Chicago NHL team?", "answer": "Blackhawks" },
{ "question": "ICE HOCKEY ğŸ’\n\n What is the nickname of the Edmonton NHL team?", "answer": "Oilers" },
{ "question": "ICE HOCKEY ğŸ’\n\n What is the nickname of the New York NHL team based in Manhattan?", "answer": "Rangers" },

  { "question": "LITERATURE ğŸ“š\n\n What is the name of the fictional wizard school in 'Harry Potter'?", "answer": "Hogwarts" },
  { "question": "LITERATURE ğŸ“š\n\n What was the title of Stephen King's first novel?", "answer": "Carrie" },
  { "question": "LITERATURE ğŸ“š\n\n Who wrote 'The Master and Margarita'?", "answer": "Bulgakov" },
  { "question": "LITERATURE ğŸ“š\n\n Complete the Shakespeare play: Timon of _____", "answer": "Athens" },
  { "question": "LITERATURE ğŸ“š\n\n Who wrote the epic poem 'Paradise Lost'?", "answer": "Milton" },

  { "question": "MYTHOLOGY ğŸ‰\n\n Who was the Greek god of the sea?", "answer": "Poseidon" },
  { "question": "MYTHOLOGY ğŸ‰\n\n What mythological creature has the body of a lion and the head of an eagle?", "answer": "Griffin" },
  { "question": "MYTHOLOGY ğŸ‰\n\n What is the name of the Roman god of war?", "answer": "Mars" },
  { "question": "MYTHOLOGY ğŸ‰\n\n What was the Roman name for the Greek goddess Hera?", "answer": "Juno" },
  { "question": "MYTHOLOGY ğŸ‰\n\n Which Olympian goddess was born fully-formed from the skull of her father Zeus?", "answer": "Athena" },

  { "question": "MUSIC ğŸµ\n\n Which artist is known for the hit single 'Rolling in the Deep'?", "answer": "Adele" },
  { "question": "MUSIC ğŸµ\n\n What was Elvis Presleyâ€™s middle name?", "answer": "Aaron" },
  { "question": "MUSIC ğŸµ\n\n Which composer wrote the 'Moonlight Sonata'?", "answer": "Beethoven" },
  { "question": "MUSIC ğŸµ\n\n Which composer wrote the 'The Four Seasons'?", "answer": "Vivaldi" },
  { "question": "MUSIC ğŸµ\n\n What 1999 song by Santana features Rob Thomas?", "answer": "Smooth" },
  { "question": "MUSIC ğŸµ\n\n Which K-pop group released 'Dynamite' in 2020?", "answer": "BTS" },
  { "question": "MUSIC ğŸµ\n\n What was the title of Ariana Grandeâ€™s 2020 album?", "answer": "Positions" },
  { "question": "MUSIC ğŸµ\n\n Which artist had a hit in 2019 with 'Truth Hurts'?", "answer": "Lizzo" },
  { "question": "MUSIC ğŸµ\n\n Which 1991 Nirvana album features the hit song 'Smells Like Teen Spirit'?", "answer": "Nevermind" },
  { "question": "MUSIC ğŸµ\n\n Which band recorded the album 'Dark Side of the Moon'?", "answer": "Pink Floyd" },
  { "question": "MUSIC ğŸµ\n\n Which British band released the song 'Wonderwall'?", "answer": "Oasis" },
  { "question": "MUSIC ğŸµ\n\n Which pop star released the album 'Lemonade' in 2016?", "answer": "Beyonce" },
  { "question": "MUSIC ğŸµ\n\n What artist is known for the song 'Hips Don't Lie'?", "answer": "Shakira" },
  { "question": "MUSIC ğŸµ\n\n What band had hits like 'Lithium' and 'Heart-Shaped Box'?", "answer": "Nirvana" },
  { "question": "MUSIC ğŸµ\n\n Who is known for the songs 'When Doves Cry' and 'Raspberry Beret'?", "answer": "Prince" },
    
  { "question": "NAME THE ARTIST ğŸ¤\n\n Name the artist from these songs: Cheap Thrills, The Greatest, Elastic Heart.", "answer": "Sia" },
  { "question": "NAME THE ARTIST ğŸ¤\n\n Name the artist from these songs: Supermassive Black Hole, Hysteria, Uprising.", "answer": "Muse" },
  { "question": "NAME THE ARTIST ğŸ¤\n\n Name the artist from these songs: Mama, I Can't Dance, Land of Confusion.", "answer": "Genesis" },
  { "question": "NAME THE ARTIST ğŸ¤\n\n Name the artist from these songs: Under Pressure, Fat-Bottomed Girls, Bicycle Race.", "answer": "Queen" },
  { "question": "NAME THE ARTIST ğŸ¤\n\n Name the artist from these songs: Clint Eastwood, Dirty Harry, On Melancholy Hill.", "answer": "Gorillaz" },
  { "question": "NAME THE ARTIST ğŸ¤\n\n Name the artist from these songs: Believe, Strong Enough, Just Like Jesse James.", "answer": "Cher" },
  { "question": "NAME THE ARTIST ğŸ¤\n\n Name the artist from these songs: Hung Up, Frozen, Vogue.", "answer": "Madonna" },
  { "question": "NAME THE ARTIST ğŸ¤\n\n Name the artist from these songs: Sunday Bloody Sunday, The Fly, Vertigo.", "answer": "U2" },
  { "question": "NAME THE ARTIST ğŸ¤\n\n Name the artist from these songs: Sad But True, Nothing Else Matters, One.", "answer": "Metallica" },
  { "question": "NAME THE ARTIST ğŸ¤\n\n Name the artist from these songs: Maria, Hanging Up The Telephone, Atomic.", "answer": "Blondie" },
  { "question": "NAME THE ARTIST ğŸ¤\n\n Name the artist from these songs: Shut Up And Drive, Unfaithful, Umbrella.", "answer": "Rihanna" },
  { "question": "NAME THE ARTIST ğŸ¤\n\n Name the artist from these songs: Common People, Disco 2000, This Is Hardcore.", "answer": "Pulp" },
  { "question": "NAME THE ARTIST ğŸ¤\n\n Name the artist from these songs: Hello, Someone Like You, Skyfall.", "answer": "Adele" },
  { "question": "NAME THE ARTIST ğŸ¤\n\n Name the artist from these songs: So What, Family Portrait, Just Like A Pill.", "answer": "Pink" },
  { "question": "NAME THE ARTIST ğŸ¤\n\n Name the artist from these songs: Without Me, White America, My Name Is.", "answer": "Eminem" },
  { "question": "NAME THE ARTIST ğŸ¤\n\n Name the artist from these songs: One Dance, God's Plan, Hotline Bling.", "answer": "Drake" },
  { "question": "NAME THE ARTIST ğŸ¤\n\n Name the artist from these songs: Always, Bad Medicine, Keep The Faith.", "answer": "Bon Jovi" },
  { "question": "NAME THE ARTIST ğŸ¤\n\n Name the artist from these songs: Edge of Glory, Bad Romance, Just Dance.", "answer": "Lady Gaga" },
    
  { "question": "OSCARS ğŸ¬\n\n What film starring Mikey Madison won the Oscar for Best Picture in 2025?", "answer": "Anora" },
  { "question": "OSCARS ğŸ¬\n\n Which James Cameron film won the Oscar for Best Picture in 1998?", "answer": "Titanic" },

  { "question": "PHILOSOPHY ğŸ§ \n\n Who is the author of 'The Republic'?", "answer": "Plato" },
  { "question": "PHILOSOPHY ğŸ§ \n\n Who wrote 'Critique of Pure Reason'?", "answer": "Kant" },

  { "question": "PHYSICS âš›ï¸\n\n What is the SI unit of force?", "answer": "Newton" },
  { "question": "PHYSICS âš›ï¸\n\n What is the SI unit of pressure?", "answer": "Pascal" },
  { "question": "PHYSICS âš›ï¸\n\n What is the SI unit of energy/work?", "answer": "Joule" },
  { "question": "PHYSICS âš›ï¸\n\n What particle carries a negative electric charge?", "answer": "Electron" },
  { "question": "PHYSICS âš›ï¸\n\n What is the SI unit of electric current?", "answer": "Ampere" },

{ "question": "HUMAN BODY ğŸ«€\n\n What is the longest bone in the human body?", "answer": "Femur" },
{ "question": "HUMAN BODY ğŸ«€\n\n Found in the ears, what is the smallest bone in the human body?", "answer": "Stapes" },
{ "question": "HUMAN BODY ğŸ«€\n\n How many phalanges are there in a human hand?", "answer": "14" },
{ "question": "HUMAN BODY ğŸ«€\n\n Where in the human body would you find the rotator cuff?", "answer": "Shoulder" },
{ "question": "HUMAN BODY ğŸ«€\n\n The word 'pulmonary' refers to which internal organ of the human body?", "answer": "Lung" },
{ "question": "HUMAN BODY ğŸ«€\n\n What name is given to the structural protein that makes up the key components of hair, skin, and nails?", "answer": "Keratin" },
    
  { "question": "SCIENCE ğŸ”¬\n\n What is the chemical symbol for Iron?", "answer": "Fe" },
  { "question": "SCIENCE ğŸ”¬\n\n What is the phenomenon where light bends as it passes through different mediums?", "answer": "Refraction" },

  { "question": "SOCCER âš½\n\n In which year did the first football World Cup take place?", "answer": "1930" },
  { "question": "SOCCER âš½\n\n What is the nickname of Newcastle United FC?", "answer": "Magpies" },
  { "question": "SOCCER âš½\n\n Who hosted (and won) the 1998 FIFA World Cup?", "answer": "France" },
  { "question": "SOCCER âš½\n\n Gareth Bale represented which country in international tournaments?", "answer": "Wales" },
  { "question": "SOCCER âš½\n\n Which English football plays their home games at Stamford Bridge?", "answer": "Chelsea" },
  { "question": "SOCCER âš½\n\n Lionel Messi spent the majority of his playing career at which European club?", "answer": "Barcelona" },
  { "question": "SOCCER âš½\n\n Who hosted the FIFA World Cup for the first time in 2022?", "answer": "Qatar" },
  { "question": "SOCCER âš½\n\n Who hosted (and won) the 1998 FIFA World Cup?", "answer": "France" },

  { "question": "SPACE ğŸŒŒ\n\n Which planet in the solar system has the most moons?", "answer": "Jupiter" },
  { "question": "SPACE ğŸŒŒ\n\n What is the term for a star's death that results in a massive explosion?", "answer": "Supernova" },
  { "question": "SPACE ğŸŒŒ\n\n What is the largest moon of Saturn?", "answer": "Titan" },
  { "question": "SPACE ğŸŒŒ\n\n Which planet has moons named after several Shakespeare characters?", "answer": "Uranus" },

  { "question": "SPORTS ğŸ†\\n\n What country hosted the 2008 Summer Olympics?", "answer": "China" },
  { "question": "SPORTS ğŸ†\n\n Dump, floater, and wipe, are terms used in which team sport?", "answer": "Volleyball" },
  { "question": "SPORTS ğŸ†\n\n In snooker, which ball has a value of six points?", "answer": "Pink" },
  { "question": "SPORTS ğŸ†\n\n What is the nickname of the New Zealand national rugby union team?", "answer": "All Blacks" },
  { "question": "SPORTS ğŸ†\n\n What is the nickname of the South African national rugby team?", "answer": "Springboks" },
  { "question": "SPORTS ğŸ†\n\n What is the nickname of the West Indies cricket team?", "answer": "Windies" },
  { "question": "SPORTS ğŸ†\n\n What is the maximum break in snooker?", "answer": "147" },
  { "question": "SPORTS ğŸ†\n\n What is the only sport to have been played on the Moon?", "answer": "Golf" },

  { "question": "TECHNOLOGY ğŸ’»\n\n What is the name of the computer programming language developed by Sun Microsystems?", "answer": "Java" },
  { "question": "TECHNOLOGY ğŸ’»\n\n What term refers to the process of converting data into a secure format?", "answer": "Encryption" },

  { "question": "TELEVISION ğŸ“º\n\n What is the name of the fictional town where 'Stranger Things' is set?", "answer": "Hawkins" },
  { "question": "TELEVISION ğŸ“º\n\n In 'Friends', what is the first name of Rossâ€™s second wife?", "answer": "Emily" },
  { "question": "TELEVISION ğŸ“º\n\n In 'Friends', what is the surname of Monica and Ross", "answer": "Gellar" },
  { "question": "TELEVISION ğŸ“º\n\n In the U.S. version of 'The Office', what is the name of the paper company?", "answer": "Dunder Mifflin" },
  { "question": "TELEVISION ğŸ“º\n\n What Netflix series features a character called 'Joe Goldberg'?", "answer": "You" },
  { "question": "TELEVISION ğŸ“º\n\n What 2020 Disney+ series focuses on the character 'Wanda Maximoff'?", "answer": "WandaVision" },
  { "question": "TELEVISION ğŸ“º\n\n What year did the series 'Stranger Things' first premiere?", "answer": "2016" },
  { "question": "TELEVISION ğŸ“º\n\n In 'The Handmaidâ€™s Tale', what is the name of the totalitarian society?", "answer": "Gilead" },
{ "question": "TELEVISION ğŸ“º\n\n In 'Ozark', what is the last name of the main family?", "answer": "Byrd" },
{ "question": "TELEVISION ğŸ“º\n\n What is the name of the city where 'Narcos' is primarily set?", "answer": "Medellin" },
{ "question": "TELEVISION ğŸ“º\n\n What show features a high schooler named Jughead Jones?", "answer": "Riverdale" },
{ "question": "TELEVISION ğŸ“º\n\n What English city is the primary setting for 'Peaky Blinders'?", "answer": "Birmingham" },
{ "question": "TELEVISION ğŸ“º\n\n In 'The Mandalorian', what is the real name of 'The Child'?", "answer": "Grogu" },
{ "question": "TELEVISION ğŸ“º\n\n What is Ofred's real first name in 'The Handmaid's Tale'?", "answer": "June" },
{ "question": "TELEVISION ğŸ“º\n\n The main character in The Walking Dead is a sheriff called Rick _____?", "answer": "Grimes" },
{ "question": "TELEVISION ğŸ“º\n\n What is the surname of the family in HBO's 'Succession'?", "answer": "Roy" },
{ "question": "TELEVISION ğŸ“º\n\n What U.S. city is HBO's 'The Wire' set in?", "answer": "Baltimore" },
{ "question": "TELEVISION ğŸ“º\n\n What is the last name of Buffy (The Vampire Slayer?", "answer": "Summers" },
{ "question": "TELEVISION ğŸ“º\n\n What is the surname of the family in 'Malcolm in the Middle'?", "answer": "Wilkerson" },
{ "question": "TELEVISION ğŸ“º\n\n Which U.S. city is the setting for 'Cheers'?", "answer": "Boston" },
{ "question": "TELEVISION ğŸ“º\n\n What is the surname of the family in 'Full House'?", "answer": "Tanner" },
{ "question": "TELEVISION ğŸ“º\n\n What is the name of the high school in 'Saved by the Bell'?", "answer": "Bayside" },

{ "question": "MATH ğŸ“\n\n What is the square root of 169?", "answer": "13" },
{ "question": "MATH ğŸ“\n\n What is 60% of 200?", "answer": "120" },
{ "question": "MATH ğŸ“\n\n What is 1000 âˆ’ 437?", "answer": "563" },
{ "question": "MATH ğŸ“\n\n What is the square root of 225?", "answer": "15" },
{ "question": "MATH ğŸ“\n\n What is 14 Ã— 14?", "answer": "196" },
{ "question": "MATH ğŸ“\n\n What is 3Â² Ã— 2?", "answer": "18" },
{ "question": "MATH ğŸ“\n\n What is the cube root of 27?", "answer": "3" },
{ "question": "MATH ğŸ“\n\n What is 90 Ã· 6?", "answer": "15" },
{ "question": "MATH ğŸ“\n\n What is 32 âˆ’ 17?", "answer": "15" },
{ "question": "MATH ğŸ“\n\n What is 3/5 of 50?", "answer": "30" },
{ "question": "MATH ğŸ“\n\n What is the square root of 196?", "answer": "14" },
{ "question": "MATH ğŸ“\n\n What is 8 Ã— 9?", "answer": "72" },
{ "question": "MATH ğŸ“\n\n What is 600 Ã· 25?", "answer": "24" },
{ "question": "MATH ğŸ“\n\n What is 10Â³?", "answer": "1000" },
{ "question": "MATH ğŸ“\n\n What is the square root of 144?", "answer": "12" },
{ "question": "MATH ğŸ“\n\n What is 15 Ã— 12?", "answer": "180" },
{ "question": "MATH ğŸ“\n\n What is the term for a triangle with all three sides of different lengths?", "answer": "Scalene" },
    
  { "question": "HISTORY ğŸ•°ï¸\n\n Which English king signed the Magna Carta in 1215?", "answer": "John" },
  { "question": "HISTORY ğŸ•°ï¸\n\n What year did the French Revolution begin?", "answer": "1789" },
  { "question": "HISTORY ğŸ•°ï¸\n\n Who was the leader of the Soviet Union during World War II?", "answer": "Stalin" },
  { "question": "HISTORY ğŸ•°ï¸\n\n Which battle marked the end of Napoleon's rule?", "answer": "Waterloo" },
  { "question": "HISTORY ğŸ•°ï¸\n\n Who was the Egyptian queen known for her alliance with Julius Caesar?", "answer": "Cleopatra" },
  { "question": "HISTORY ğŸ•°ï¸\n\n What was the name of the ship Charles Darwin sailed on?", "answer": "Beagle" },
  { "question": "HISTORY ğŸ•°ï¸\n\n Which empire built Machu Picchu?", "answer": "Inca" },
  { "question": "HISTORY ğŸ•°ï¸\n\n Who was assassinated on the Ides of March in 44 BC?", "answer": "Caesar" },
  { "question": "HISTORY ğŸ•°ï¸\n\n What was the name of the first permanent English settlement in America?", "answer": "Jamestown" },
  { "question": "HISTORY ğŸ•°ï¸\n\n Which treaty ended World War I?", "answer": "Versailles" },
  { "question": "HISTORY ğŸ•°ï¸\n\n Who was the last pharaoh of Ancient Egypt?", "answer": "Cleopatra" },
  { "question": "HISTORY ğŸ•°ï¸\n\n In which year did the American Civil War start?", "answer": "1861" },
  { "question": "HISTORY ğŸ•°ï¸\n\n Which empire was ruled by Suleiman the Magnificent?", "answer": "Ottoman" },
  { "question": "HISTORY ğŸ•°ï¸\n\n What was the name of the ship on which the Pilgrims traveled to America?", "answer": "Mayflower" },
  { "question": "HISTORY ğŸ•°ï¸\n\n Who invented the printing press?", "answer": "Gutenberg" },
  { "question": "HISTORY ğŸ•°ï¸\n\n What was the main language of the Roman Empire?", "answer": "Latin" },
  { "question": "HISTORY ğŸ•°ï¸\n\n What was the first man-made object to orbit Earth?", "answer": "Sputnik" },
  { "question": "HISTORY ğŸ•°ï¸\n\n In which year did World War II end?", "answer": "1945" },
  { "question": "HISTORY ğŸ•°ï¸\n\n Who was the second President of the United States?", "answer": "Adams" },
  { "question": "HISTORY ğŸ•°ï¸\n\n What year did the Titanic sink?", "answer": "1912" },
  { "question": "HISTORY ğŸ•°ï¸\n\n In what year did the Berlin Wall fall?", "answer": "1989" },
  { "question": "HISTORY ğŸ•°ï¸\n\n In what year was the Magna Carta signed?", "answer": "1215" },
  { "question": "HISTORY ğŸ•°ï¸\n\n Which ancient civilization used a system of writing called cuneiform?", "answer": "Sumerian" },
  { "question": "HISTORY ğŸ•°ï¸\n\n Which country was once known as Ceylon?", "answer": "Sri Lanka" },
  { "question": "HISTORY ğŸ•°ï¸\n\n What is the oldest active language still spoken?", "answer": "Tamil" },
  { "question": "HISTORY ğŸ•°ï¸\n\n Which empire built the Great Wall of China?", "answer": "Qin" },
  { "question": "HISTORY ğŸ•°ï¸\n\n Which ancient civilization is famous for building Machu Picchu?", "answer": "Inca" },
  { "question": "HISTORY ğŸ•°ï¸\n\n Who was the last pharaoh of Egypt?", "answer": "Cleopatra" },
  { "question": "HISTORY ğŸ•°ï¸\n\n Who was the first emperor of Rome?", "answer": "Augustus" },
  { "question": "HISTORY ğŸ•°ï¸\n\n Who became the second emperor of Rome after Augustus?", "answer": "Tiberius" },

  { "question": "MIXED BAG ğŸ²\n\n Dulse, kelp, and bladder-wrack are types of what?", "answer": "Seaweed" },
  { "question": "MIXED BAG ğŸ²\n\n Which stadium holds the world record for having the most toilets with over two-and-a-half thousand in total?", "answer": "Wembley" },
  { "question": "MIXED BAG ğŸ²\n\n Which company began as a playing card manufacturer in the nineteenth-century before becoming famous for video game consoles?", "answer": "Nintendo" },
  { "question": "MIXED BAG ğŸ²\n\n What drink â€“ often considered the oldest alcoholic drink ever discovered â€“ is made from fermenting honey and water?", "answer": "Mead" },

  { "question": "NATURAL WORLD ğŸŒ¿\n\n Red Admiral and Painted Lady are types of which insect?", "answer": "Butterfly" },
  { "question": "NATURAL WORLD ğŸŒ¿\n\n Fledermaus is the German name for which mammal?", "answer": "Bat" },
  { "question": "NATURAL WORLD ğŸŒ¿\n\n The world's largest lizard species, the Komodo dragon, is native to which continent?", "answer": "Asia" },
  { "question": "NATURAL WORLD ğŸŒ¿\n\n A samoyed is a breed of which domesticated animal?", "answer": "Dog" },
  { "question": "NATURAL WORLD ğŸŒ¿\n\n Dromedary and Bactrian are the two main species of which animal?", "answer": "Camel" },
  { "question": "NATURAL WORLD ğŸŒ¿\n\n Which prickly plant with a rounded head of purple flowers is a national emblem of Scotland?", "answer": "Thistle" },

  { "question": "WEAPONS âš”ï¸\n\n What would be produced by a medieval craftsman known as a fletcher?", "answer": "Arrows" },
  { "question": "WEAPONS âš”ï¸\n\n What name is given to a type of Native American axe that can also refer to a cut of steak?", "answer": "Tomahawk" },
  { "question": "WEAPONS âš”ï¸\n\n Which African country has an image of an AK47 rifle on their national flag?", "answer": "Mozambique" },
  { "question": "WEAPONS âš”ï¸\n\n What name is given to both a three-pronged spear and the United Kingdom's nuclear weapons programme?", "answer": "Trident" },

{ "question": "ANIMALS ğŸ¶\n\n What animal is known as the only truly flightless parrot?", "answer": "Kakapo" },
{ "question": "ANIMALS ğŸ¶\n\n Which small marsupial is known for its 'smiling' appearance?", "answer": "Quokka" },
{ "question": "ANIMALS ğŸ¶\n\n Which large rodent is the biggest in the world?", "answer": "Capybara" },
{ "question": "ANIMALS ğŸ¶\n\n Which marine mammal has a long, spiral tusk?", "answer": "Narwhal" },
{ "question": "ANIMALS ğŸ¶\n\n Which ant-eating mammal resembles a fox but belongs to the hyena family?", "answer": "Aardwolf" },
{ "question": "ANIMALS ğŸ¶\n\n Which dog was sent into space by the Soviet Union in 1957, becoming the first animal to orbit the Earth?", "answer": "Laika" },
{ "question": "ANIMALS ğŸ¶\n\n Dalmatians originated in the region of Dalmatia in which European country?", "answer": "Croatia" },
{ "question": "ANIMALS ğŸ¶\n\n Which German dog breed is often referred to as a 'sausage dog'?", "answer": "Daschund" },
{ "question": "ANIMALS ğŸ¶\n\n What desert fox is known for its oversized ears?", "answer": "Fennec" },

{ "question": "FLOWERS ğŸŒ¸\n\n What flower is traditionally worn on Remembrance Day in the United Kingdom?", "answer": "Poppy" },
{ "question": "FLOWERS ğŸŒ¸\n\n Which flowering plant is the main source of vanilla?", "answer": "Orchid" },
{ "question": "FLOWERS ğŸŒ¸\n\n Which flower is the national emblem of France?", "answer": "Iris" },
{ "question": "FLOWERS ğŸŒ¸\n\n Which flower is a national symbol of Wales and known for its trumpet-shaped bloom?", "answer": "Daffodil" },
{ "question": "FLOWERS ğŸŒ¸\n\n What is the national flower of India?", "answer": "Lotus" },
{ "question": "FLOWERS ğŸŒ¸\n\n Which alpine flower is known for growing in high mountain ranges and symbolizes courage?", "answer": "Edelweiss" },


]
